Social Justice Center; Records apap177
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
Social Justice Center Records
1981-2001
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
Social Justice Center
apap177
4.3 cubic ft. 54 Digital Files 19 VHS tapes
The Center was formed in 1981 by an alliance of non-profit activist organizations in order to provide a central location, office space, and basic services for activist groups in Albany, New York.
Administrative History
The Social Justice Center (SJC) was formed in 1981 by an alliance of nonprofit activist organizations in order to provide a central location, office space, and basic services for activist groups in Albany, New York. The SJC was originally known as the Social Action Center, but the name was changed sometime in the late 1980s. Both names were used interchangeably for a period of time. The first product of the alliance was the Unity Statement, which laid out the goals and philosophy of the SJC. Groups in agreement with the Unity Statement were able to join the SJC and receive inexpensive office space and services. Membership varies, but currently there are around twenty member groups.
The functioning of the Center was originally overseen by the Coordinating Committee, which was composed of one representative from each member group. The Coordinating Committee was responsible for accepting or denying groups, setting policy, hiring staff and creating subcommittees for handling finances or performing certain projects. It was later decided that a more formal board was needed, and in 1996 a Board of Directors was formed from progressive members of the community. The Center currently employs a director, Victorio Reyes.
The center initially leased property and was eventually able to purchase and renovate a building in downtown Albany at 33 Central Avenue. The grand opening of this building was in April 1987. The storefront of the building is occupied by Peace Offerings, a gift shop and project of the Social Justice Center. Billed as The Store with a Social Conscience, Peace Offerings buys products from artisan collectives in developing countries and its sales directly fund the SJC. The store first opened in 1984 as a fundraiser during the Christmas holiday season. It was successful enough that in 1989 it became a permanent, yearround store. Peace Offerings is staffed by two parttime employees, a manager and a bookkeeper. The Social Justice Center and Peace Offerings combined operate with over sixty volunteers.
Other projects of the Center include the Dismantling Racism project, which sponsors workshops to address the roots of racial prejudice, the PCB/Environmental Health project, which works to educate the community about potential toxins, and the Infoshop, a lending library that stocks progressive periodicals and books.
The founding groups of the SJC include the Albany Peace and Energy Council, the Committee for a New Korea Policy, the New York State Citizens Party, Rights for American Indians Now, and the Knolls Action Project. Since its founding, the center has housed a number of organizations, including Campus Action, the National Lawyers Guild, Citizens Environmental Coalition, New York Bicycling Coalition, the Homeless Action Committee, and the Institute for Farmworker Justice.
Several collections in the M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives provide further information about the issues of concern to the Social Justice Center. For a complete list of related collections see the subject guides for Conservation and the Environment, African American and Civil Rights Organizations, Human Sexuality and Gender Identity, Social Activists and Public Advocates, and Women. Of particular note are the collections of organizations and individuals which were members of the Social Justice Center or worked with the SJC on projects. These collections include the records of Citizens Environmental Coalition (APAP197), Campus Action (APAP164), Knolls Action Project (APAP105), Capital District Coalition Against Apartheid and Racism (APAP011), Save The Pine Bush (APAP125), New York Coalition For Alternatives to Pesticides (APAP151), ACT UP Albany (APAP106), the Capital District Committee For Palestinian Rights (APAP163), Tom Nattell (APAP191) who was a founding member of the Albany Peace and Energy Council, and Lawrence Wittner (APAP100) of the Democratic Socialists of America and other organizations.
Scope and Contents
The records of the Social Justice Center contain materials generated and collected by its staff, including financial records, meeting minutes, publications, fliers, grant proposals, photographs, and correspondence. There are also materials generated by the operation of the store Peace Offerings, including log books, inventories, and time sheets as well as promotional materials, such as signs, educational hand outs, and videos.
The history, goals, and operations of the SJC is well represented in the Administrative Files series, particularly in the meeting minutes of the Coordinating Committee. Histories of the center can be found in the 1991 board retreat material. The Peace Offering series primarily contains promotional materials such as signs and displays. There is a small amount of administrative material for the gift store, primarily found in the minutes of the Steering Committee. There is also a small amount of electronic records in the Peace Offerings series, split between administrative material and material for a Developing MultiCulturalism conference.
There is little material in this collection from the member groups of the SJC. There is a small amount of administrative materials from the Centro de Progresso group and a folder of materials from the creation of the Institute for Farmworker Justice, but all other materials consist of general publications that can be found in the Subject File series. Lists of the member groups can be drawn from the items in the brochures folder or from the financial records in the group billing folders.
Arrangement of the Collection
The collection is organized into 3 file series.
Acquisition Information
All items in this manuscript group were donated to the University Libraries, M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives by the Social Justice Center in 2004 May.
Access
Access to this record group is unrestricted.
Social movements -- New York (State).; Peace movements -- New York (State).; Civil rights movements -- New York (State).; Social justice -- New York (State).; Demonstrations -- New York (State).; Environmental justice -- New York (State).; Polychlorinated biphenyls.; Minutes.; Correspondence.; Brochures.; Videotapes.; Newsletters.; Photographs.; African Americans and Civil Rights Organizations; Albany, New York; Conservation and the Environment; Neighborhood and Community Associations; Social Activists and Public Advocates; Medicine and Health Care; Women; Military and Armed Conflict; Human Sexuality and Gender Identity; Digital Files; Reyes, Victorio.; Peace Offerings.; Centro de Progreso.; Institute of Farmworkers Justice.
- Administrative Files, 1981-2001; 1; 1 cubic ft. 24 Digital Files
  Arrangement
  Arranged alphabetically, with electronic records at the end.
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains records generated by the Social Justice Center in the process of its ongoing mission to provide space and services to social justice organizations. The records include financial reports, correspondence, and meeting minutes from the Coordinating Committee and later the centers board. Also included are documents related to fundraising, including dance and walk-a-thons, grant proposals, and related materials. The records of the Centro de Progresso, the only member group of the SJC with material in this collection, can be found in this series. Finally, there is a small amount of material in Electronic File format from the planning of a workshop of the Dismantling Racism project.
  - Activist Newsletter, 1991-1993 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 1)
  - Almanac for Social Justice, 1989 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 2)
  - April Mobilization Coalition, 1987 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 3)
  - Awards Dinner Programs, 1991-1992 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 4)
  - Board, Meeting Minutes, Agendas, 1996-1999 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 5)
  - Board Invitation, 1997; Undated (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 6)
  - Board Retreat, Background Material, 1983; 1991; Undated (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 7)
  - Board Retreat, Board Member Packet, 1997 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 8)
  - Brochures, Undated (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 9)
  - Building, Photographs, Undated (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 10)
  - Community Works Social Action Fund, Meeting Minutes, Reports, Correspondence, 1993-1994; Undated (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 11)
  - Coordinating Committee, Meeting Minutes, Reports, Correspondence, 1985; 1988-1993 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 1982-1997; 2000; Undated (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 13)
  - Creation of Social Justice Center, Correspondence, 1981 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 14)
  - Evaluation Meeting, Minutes, 1988 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 15)
  - Financial Reports, 1984-1987 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 16)
  - Financial Reports, 1994 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 17)
  - Fliers, 1982; 1987; 1993; Undated (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 18)
  - Fundraising, Dance-a-thon, Corporate Sponsorship, 1996-1997 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 19)
  - Fundraising, Dance-a-thon, Logistics, 1996-1997 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 20)
  - Fundraising, Dance-a-thon, Participants, 1996-1997 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 21)
  - Fundraising, Dance-a-thon, Promotional Material, 1994-1996; Undated (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 22)
  - Fundraising, Raffle, Correspondence, Flier, 1993-1994 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 23)
  - Fundraising, Walk-a-thon, 1984 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 24)
  - Grants, A.J. Muste Memorial Institute, 1995 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 25)
  - Grants, Chase Racial Harmony and Diversity Program, Grant Proposal, 1996-1997 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 26)
  - Grants, Miscellaneous Grant Proposals, 1989; 1993; 1996 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 27)
  - Grants, Public Welfare Foundation, Grant Proposal, 1985; 1998 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 28)
  - Group Billing, 1989 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 29)
  - Group Billing, 1992 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 30)
  - Group Billing, 1994 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 31)
  - Group Billing, 1995-1996 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 32)
  - History, 1991 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 33)
  - Honoring the Leadership of Women of Color for Social Change, Photographs, Negatives, 1991; Undated (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 34)
  - Mailing List, Undated (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 35)
  - Member Group Applications, Contracts, 1985 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 36)
  - Member Groups, Centro de Progreso, By-Laws, Fliers, Newspaper Clippings, 1999-2000; Undated (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 37)
  - Member Groups, Centro de Progreso Correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 38)
  - Member Groups, Centro de Progreso, Correspondence, Charity Auto Choice, 1999 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 39)
  - Member Groups, Centro de Progreso, Fund Raiser Responses, 1998 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 40)
  - Member Groups, Centro de Progreso, Holding Our Own, Grant Proposal, 1999 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 41)
  - Member Groups, Centro de Progreso, Meeting Minutes, Notes, 1998-1999 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 42)
  - Member Groups, Institute for Farmworkers Justice, Notes, Undated (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 43)
  - Member Groups, Latino Journal, 1992-1993 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 44)
  - Memoranda, Peace Offerings, 1985; 1993; Undated (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 45)
  - Move to 33 Central Ave., History of Property, 1987 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 46)
  - Move to 33 Central Ave., Renovations, Correspondence, Estimate, Notes, 1987 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 47)
  - Notes, 1988; 1992; Undated (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 48)
  - Outlets for Advertising, 1995 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 49)
  - Peace and Justice Awards, Press Releases, 1987; 1992 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 50)
  - Promotional Table at Events, Correspondence, Conference Materials, 1991-1993 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 51)
  - Promotional Table at Events, Correspondence, 1994 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 52)
  - Promotional Table at Events, Correspondence, Festival Materials, 1995 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 53)
  - Promotions, Correspondence, Publications, Notes, 1994-1995 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 54)
  - Readings Against The End Of The World, Correspondence, 1986 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 55)
  - Toxics In Your Community Coalition, 1990 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 56)
  - Unity Statement, Undated (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 57)
  - Dismantling Racism Project Workshop, Agenda, 2000
  - Dismantling Racism Project Workshop, Agenda, Project SANO, 1999
  - Dismantling Racism Project Workshop, Birth Plan, 1999
  - Dismantling Racism Project Workshop, Community Voices, 1999
  - Dismantling Racism Project Workshop, Curriculum Continuity Sheet, 2000
  - Dismantling Racism Project Workshop, Curriculum Options, 2000
  - Dismantling Racism Project Workshop, Diagram, 1998
  - Dismantling Racism Project Workshop, Four Working Assumptions, 1999
  - Dismantling Racism Project Workshop, Gender Definitions, 1999
  - Dismantling Racism Project Workshop, Logistics Agenda, 1999
  - Dismantling Racism Project Workshop, Materials To Do List, 1999
  - Dismantling Racism Project Workshop, Nasiima, 2000
  - Dismantling Racism Project Workshop, Note From Breakout Session, 1999
  - Dismantling Racism Project Workshop, Outreach, 1999
  - Dismantling Racism Project Workshop, Phone List, 2000
  - Dismantling Racism Project Workshop, Revitalization Meeting, 1999
  - Dismantling Racism Project Workshop, Stage of Organization, 1999
  - Dismantling Racism Project Workshop, Things To Keep In Mind, 1999
  - Dismantling Racism Project Workshop, To Do List, 1999
  - Dismantling Racism Project Workshop, Wheel of Oppression, 1999
  - Dismantling Racism Project Workshop, White Privilege, 1999
  - Dismantling Racism Project Workshop, Womens Bean Project Questions, 2000
  - Dismantling Racism Project Workshop, Work Plan, 2000
  - Dismantling Racism Project Workshop, Working Assumption, 1998
- Peace Offerings, 1984-1995; 2; 1 cubic ft. 30 Digital Files
  This series is comprised of records generated by the store Peace Offerings in its day-to-day operations as a gift shop. This includes log sheets, inventories, time sheets, and meeting minutes of the steering committee. In addition, this series contains promotional materials from the store and from vendors, such as signs, press releases, fliers, and educational videos. This series also contains materials from the Cultural Marketplace Tour, where artisans from Mexico, Bolivia, and Ecuador visited the store. There is also a small amount of electronic records in this series, split between administrative material and conference material for the Dismantling Racism Project.
  - Activities, Fliers, Press Releases, 1996 (Box 1 (2-Peace Offerings), Folder 1)
  - Artisan Information for Store Display, Undated (Box 1 (2-Peace Offerings), Folder 2)
  - Certificates of Appreciation for Volunteers, Undated (Box 1 (2-Peace Offerings), Folder 3)
  - Cooperative Games, Notes, Undated (Box 1 (2-Peace Offerings), Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1986; 1992-1996; Undated (Box 1 (2-Peace Offerings), Folder 5)
  - Cultural Marketplace Tour, Albany Arts Commission Grant, Correspondence, Grant Proposal, Notes, 1995 (Box 1 (2-Peace Offerings), Folder 6)
  - Cultural Marketplace Tour, News Clippings, 1995; Undated (Box 1 (2-Peace Offerings), Folder 7)
  - Cultural Marketplace Tour, Correspondence, Fliers, Notes, Schedules, 1995; Undated (Box 1 (2-Peace Offerings), Folder 8)
  - Financial Records, 1989-1994 (Box 1 (2-Peace Offerings), Folder 9)
  - Fundraising Nights, Mailing, Address List, Undated (Box 1 (2-Peace Offerings), Folder 10)
  - History, 1986; 1988-1991 (Box 1 (2-Peace Offerings), Folder 11)
  - Inventories, 1994 (Box 1 (2-Peace Offerings), Folder 12)
  - Inventories, 1995 (Box 1 (2-Peace Offerings), Folder 13)
  - Inventories, 1995 (Box 1 (2-Peace Offerings), Folder 14)
  - Listing of Alternative Trade Organizations, Global Exchange, Undated (Box 1 (2-Peace Offerings), Folder 15)
  - Log Books, Notebooks, Undated (Box 1 (2-Peace Offerings), Folder 16)
  - Log Sheets, 1993 March-August (Box 1 (2-Peace Offerings), Folder 17)
  - Log Sheets, 1993 September-1994 May (Box 1 (2-Peace Offerings), Folder 18)
  - Press Releases, Media Contact Lists, 1988-1993 (Box 1 (2-Peace Offerings), Folder 19)
  - Project Proposals, 1984; 1986 (Box 1 (2-Peace Offerings), Folder 20)
  - Promotional and Educational Signs, Undated (Box 1 (2-Peace Offerings), Folder 21)
  - Promotional Ideas, News Clippings, Leaflets, Correspondence, 1991-1993; Undated (Box 1 (2-Peace Offerings), Folder 22)
  - Promotions, Fliers, Notes, Correspondence, 1993-1995; Undated (Box 1 (2-Peace Offerings), Folder 23)
  - Shoplifting, Meeting Minutes, Notes, Flier, 1995; Undated (Box 1 (2-Peace Offerings), Folder 24)
  - Sponsorship, WAMC, WMHT, 1994 (Box 1 (2-Peace Offerings), Folder 25)
  - Staff Folder, Correspondence, 1993 (Box 1 (2-Peace Offerings), Folder 26)
  - Steering Committee, Meeting Minutes, Agendas, 1986; 1993-1995 (Box 1 (2-Peace Offerings), Folder 27)
  - Store Layout, Diagrams, Undated (Box 1 (2-Peace Offerings), Folder 28)
  - Vendor Questionnaires, 1998; Undated (Box 1 (2-Peace Offerings), Folder 29)
  - Volunteer Meetings, Fliers, Calendar, Agenda, Undated (Box 1 (2-Peace Offerings), Folder 30)
  - Volunteer Staff Training, Undated (Box 1 (2-Peace Offerings), Folder 31)
  - Videos, Undated
  - Ad Mailing, 1994
  - Budget, 1994
  - Budgeting For Festivals, 1997
  - Cultural Marketplace Mailing, 1995
  - Cultural Marketplace Outline, 1995
  - Educate The Children (ETC) Profile, 1994
  - Fair Trade Federation Members, 1994
  - Job Description, Temporary Store Manager, 1994
  - Latino Collegiate Conference, 1996
  - Learning Contract, Kimberly Manning, 1997
  - Learning Contract, Ryan Walsh, 1997
  - Loans, 1994
  - Meeting Agenda, 1995 February
  - Meeting Minutes, 1994 July
  - Meeting Minutes, 1995 March
  - Meeting Minutes, 1995 April
  - Meeting Minutes, 1995 May
  - Meeting Minutes, 1995 July
  - Meeting Minutes, 1995 September
  - Meeting Minutes, 1996 January
  - Nagasaki Press Release, 1995
  - Promotion Timeline, 1994
  - Proposal For Consignments, 1994
  - Staffing Proposal, 1997
  - Tax Letter, 1996
  - Timeline, 1994
  - Timeline, 1995
  - Vendor List, 1995
  - Vendor Questionnaire, 1995
  - Volunteer List, 1996
- Subject Files, 1987-1997; 3; 2.3 cubic ft.
  Arranged alphabetically.
  The Subject Files series contains mostly publications collected by the Social Justice Center and Peace Offerings from other organizations, such as newsletters and educational materials. Much of the material originates from the SELFHELP Crafts organization, which later became Ten Thousand Villages. Also included are research materials on the issues related to PCBs, environmental clean-up, and environmental justice.
  - Albany/Schenectady League of Arts, 1992-1993 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Alternative Trade Organizations, Publications, Leaflets, Correspondence, 1990-1992; Undated (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Alternative Trade Organization Questionnaire, Correspondence, 1997 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Community Building as a Process for Social Change, Article, Undated (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Community Organizations, List, Undated (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Co-op America Quarterly, Magazine, 1996-1997 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Customs and Importing, US Government Publications, 1988-1991 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Dinner, Photographs, Undated (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Educational Material, 1994; Undated (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Fair Trade Federation, 1993; 1995; 1998 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Family Planning Advocates, Fliers, Leaflets, Publications, 1997; Undated (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Film and Video Resources, Catalogs, Fliers, Correspondence, 1992; Undated (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Hand in Hand Store, Year End Report, 1991 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Homeless Action Committee, Undated (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Lesbian and Gay Community Funding Partnership, 1995 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Magazines, 1994-1995; 1997 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - March on Washington for Lesbian and Gay Rights, Photographs, Negatives, 1987 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Newsletter, Connections, 1996-1997 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Newsletter, Craft News, 1992-1995 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Newsletter, Educate the Children (E.T.C), 1992-1993; 1995 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Newsletter, Gayzette, 1996-1997 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Newsletter, Global Link, 1997 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Newsletter, In The Life, 1996 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Newsletter, Miscellaneous, 1991-1997 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Newsletter, Networks, 1993-1995; 1997 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Newsletter, Partnerships, 1995-1996 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Newsletter, SERRV Handcrafts Connection, 1990-1994 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - North American Alternative Trade Conference, Conference Materials, 1991-1993 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - North American Alternative Trade Conference, Conference Materials, 1994 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - North American Alternative Trade Conference, Photographs, Negatives, 1994 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Pamphlets, Undated (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - PCBs, 1995-1996; Undated (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - PCBs, News Clippings, 1984-1991; 1993-1996 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - "Sadako and the Thousand Paper Cranes," Newsletters, News Clippings, 1991; 1993-1994; Undated (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - SELFHELP Crafts, Educational Materials, 1986; 1990; Undated (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - SELFHELP Crafts, Educational Materials, Haiti, Dominican Republic, 1990; Undated (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - SELFHELP Crafts, Educational Materials, India, Undated (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - SELFHELP Crafts, Educational Materials, Indonesian, 1991 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - SELFHELP Crafts, Educational Materials, Kenya, Botswana, Undated (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - SELFHELP Crafts, Educational Materials, Laos, 1991; Undated (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 40)
  - SELFHELP Crafts, Educational Materials, Mexico, Peru, 1993; 1997; Undated (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 41)
  - SELFHELP Crafts, Educational Materials, Nepal, 1991; 1997; Undated (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 42)
  - SELFHELP Crafts, Educational Materials, Pakistan, 1991; Undated (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 43)